### Shalom Odozi

🗣 Flat 10 Paris corte, 75 Loampit vale, SE13 7FN, United Kingdom 💹 shalomodozi7@gmail.com

07572592505

### **Profile**

I am a highly motivated and forward-thinking graduate, who is eager to learn. My Pharmacology degree has given me

confidence to work with large amounts of data, and become very analytical and critical in my thinking. I have a passion for technology and have self taught python. From there, my work experience has introduced me to several other technologies such as Java, mySQL and different forms of testing including test automation and manual testing. In my free time, I have been continuing to build my skills with HTML, CSS and JavaScript and Docker. With almost 4 years experience in the

hospitality sector I can provide outstanding customer service, work in a fast paced environment and keep up with demand. I am seeking an opportunity to utilise my transferable skills in an outstanding company.

Skills		
• Java	• CSS3	• HTML5
• SQL	• Docker	• Selenium webdriver
• Cucumber	Gherkin	• Python

### **Professional Experience**

### 04/2020 - present

#### Ten10

Graduate trainee/Junior consultant

- Worked well in teams on several projects, completing test scripts, test sessions, finding bugs and logging it in JIRA.
- Completed a small project using mySQL.
- Tested websites using selenium webdriver and Java, Cucumber and Gherkin.
- Used Agile methodologies when completing projects and using GIT
- Learnt Java and used it to create several games and in Test automation.
- Looked into web development and created a practice website.

### 06/2016 - 02/2020

## Urban people, Harris & Porter recruitment, High society (hospitality agencies)

Bar staff, Waiting and Cashier

- I provided excellent customer service at various events and venues including Weddings, Stadiums and Festivals.
- Worked in teams to provide simultaneous food and drink service.
- Counted stock before and after a shift for inventory management
- · Replenished stock throughout shifts.
- Used the till system to complete transactions
- Dealt with customer enquiries and progressed it to the Manager when necessary
- I represented my agencies very well, by showing good communication, initiative, punctuality and teamwork. Clients have requested to work with me again.

07/2018 - 08/2018

# London interdisciplinary doctoral programme with Doctor Sula at Birbeck college

Intern

- I assisted Dr Sula with a range of experiments and learned different experimental techniques
- I processed and analysed large amounts of data generated in order to identify the target subject
- Interpreted the data in order to present the findings to colleagues and fellow academics so it was understandable to the public.
- I was able to follow instructions and use my own initiative in certain experiments to give a better outcome.

### **Education**

### 09/2016 - 05/2019

### **University of Hertfordshire**

Pharmacology

Key modules include pharmacology, bioscience and research methods.

Transferable skills learnt:

- Analytical: Performed a range of experiments and analysed the data to produce lab reports and wrote a literature review on potassium channels.
- Worked with large amounts of complex data in my dissertation, where I organised, interpreted and presented the data so it was easy to understand.
- Teamwork/Presentation: Presented a range of assignments from scientific posters from scientific posters to clinical stimulation where we received high grades.
- Time management: Managed my time with assignment deadlines, coordinating group works and exam revisions.

2014 - 2016

### **Chislehurt and Sidcup grammar school**

A-Levels studied- Biology, Chemistry and History

2009 - 2014

### **Eltham Hill School**

Obtained 11 A\* to Cs in GCSE's

### **Interests**

Reading

Crochet

• Gym

· Watching documentaries.